export const quiz = {
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'True of False. Less trees mean colder temperatures',
        answers: ['True', 'False'],
        correctAnswer: 'False',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'What do trees give out?',
        answers: ['Chocolate', 'Oxygen', 'Carbon Dioxide', 'Eggs'],
        correctAnswer: 'Oxygen',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Whats the percentage of trees that could be destroyed by 2050?',
        answers: ['25%', '50%', '40%', '35%'],
        correctAnswer: '40%',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'True of False. Cutting down trees makes better homes for animals',
        answers: ['True', 'False'],
        correctAnswer: 'False',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What can you do to stop this',
        answers: ['Cry', 'Plant more trees', 'Cut more trees', 'Do nothing'],
        correctAnswer: 'Plant more trees',
      
      },
    ],
  };
  
  export const quizz = {
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'True or False. Global Warming helps to make more ice',
        answers: ['True', 'False'],
        correctAnswer: 'False. It actually melts the ice',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Who is more in danger when ice melts?',
        answers: ['Animals', 'Sky', 'Batman', 'People'],
        correctAnswer: 'Animals',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What type of Pengiuns could be extinct by 2050?',
        answers: ['King Pengiun', 'African Pengiun', 'Emperor Pengiun', 'Little Pengiun'],
        correctAnswer: 'Emperor Pengiun',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Who causes the most damage to Antarctica',
        answers: ['Iron-Man', 'People', 'Animals', 'Messi'],
        correctAnswer: 'People',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'True or False. 150 billion metric tons of ice melt a year',
        answers: ['True','False'],
        correctAnswer: 'True',
      },
    ],
  };
  
  export const quizzz = {
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'True or False. Bamboo is not the right food for Pandas',
        answers: ['True', 'False'],
        correctAnswer: 'True. They need to eat so much',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Why is Global Warming endagering Polar Bears?',
        answers: ['Less sun', 'Ice is melting away', 'too much water', 'no more wind'],
        correctAnswer: 'Ice is melting away',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Why do Snow leopards get hunted?',
        answers: ['Fur and bones', 'Selfie', 'Dangerous', 'Its fun'],
        correctAnswer: 'Fur and bones',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'True of False. There are 5 extinct Tigers',
        answers: ['True', 'False'],
        correctAnswer: 'False. There is only 3',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'How many Turtles get hunted a year?',
        answers: ['500,000', '225,000', '250,000', '150,000'],
        correctAnswer: '250,000',
      },
    ],
  };
  


